<tarihce>
<part>
<tarih>1936</tarih>
<aciklama> In 1936 our founder Ahmet TUNAY started Scale and Truck Scale production with the brand registered in his own name. </aciklama>
<img>1936.png</img>
</part>
<part>
<tarih>1965</tarih>
<aciklama> The facilities which were started in İstanbul- Ayvansaray transported to our factory which was founded in Beylikdüzü and we started our first regular Truck Scale production. </aciklama>
<img>1965.png</img>
</part>
<part>
<tarih>1975</tarih>
<aciklama> In 1975 our brand name was changed to "TUNAYLAR" and registered. </aciklama>
<img>1975.png</img>
</part>
<part>
<tarih>1978</tarih>
<aciklama> In order to meet growing needs and demands, our company enlarged the 450m2 factory to 3000m2 closed are in beylikdüzü and continued its facilities </aciklama>
<img>1978.png</img>
</part>
<part>
<tarih>1980</tarih>
<aciklama> In 1980 the first Electronic Truck Scale in our country was manufactured by our company. </aciklama>
<img>1980.png</img>
</part>
<part>
<tarih>1985</tarih>
<aciklama> In 1985 besides our main subject, truck scales, we started to produce electronic floor scales of various types and capacities between 3kg - 20 ton with respect to customer requirements.</aciklama>
<img>1985.png</img>
</part>
<part>
<tarih>1998</tarih>
<aciklama>In 1998 our company started to produce electronic weight and weighing indicators and accessories of its own name.</aciklama>
<img>1998.png</img>
</part>
<part>
<tarih>2002</tarih>
<aciklama> In 2002 ISO 9001: 2000 Quality Management System certificate was received from UKAS Accreditation service.</aciklama>
<img>2002.png</img>
</part>
<part>
<tarih>2005</tarih>
<aciklama> The ISO 9001:2000 quality management system of Tunaylar meets the customers expectations at the highest level by its product and system certificates, valid at national and international fields such as 90/384 EC Type Approval, CE, Metrological CE, OIML, GOST and so on. The European Type Approval certification of our truck scales, produced at international standards under this scope, is carried out by Delta that is one of the organizations authorized by the European Commission. The EC verification and sealing procedures of our truck scales that are used within the scope of legal metrology, are carried out by our company under the NMI notified body accreditation (CE044) and put in use accordingly. 
</aciklama>
<img>2005.png</img>
</part>
<part>
<tarih>2007</tarih>
<aciklama> In 2007 our ISO 9001:2000 certificate was renewed with the TÜV-CERT ISO 9001:2008 certificate, which was granted by TÜV Rheinland Technical Control and Documentation Inc. as a result of its auditing process.</aciklama>
<img>2007.png</img>
</part>
<part>
<tarih>2011</tarih>
<aciklama> Our Company that modernized its production processes anew together with our new plant that has been completed in 2011 at the district Esenyurt of Istanbul and covered an area of 7000 m2. In accordance with the international norms and technological developments has supported the manufacturing processes due to elapsed from the entry of raw materials up to the dying and shipment of the finished product with up-to-date machinery and equipments in consideration of the matters such as mass production as well as more quality production and come to a position where it is able to meet perpetually increasing domestic and international demands in a shorter period by the standards, created in this respect. </aciklama>
<img>2008.png</img>
</part>
<part>
<tarih>2013</tarih>
<aciklama>Tunaylar laboratory which has been operating for two years was accredited within the scope of non-automatic electronic scales and mass sets according to the TS EN ISO/IEC standards by TURKAK Turkish Accreditation Agency. Welding quality and method for production process was documented by DIN EN 15085-2 certificate.
Our production facility was renovated again according to the developments in our country and around the world in recent years under the terms of sale and competition conditions. In this direction, our production capacity is 2-fold increased within “SCALE MASTER” machinery park which has new CNC controlled machinery and robotic welding lines. At the same time, the products with TUNAYLAR brand name has started to take up more space in the global market by rearranging export activities through cooperation and representation agreements with many countries, including the far east.
</aciklama>
<img>2013.png</img>
</part>
</tarihce>